





Contacts:

- postilha.a@gmail.com
- +38(093)362-18-71
- https://t.me/a_z_3_8

Skills:

- PHP (Laravel)
- REST API
- MySQL
- Bash
- Git & GitHub
- HTML
- CSS
- Python (Django)
- Figma

Languages:

- English (B2)
- Ukrainian
- Russian

Oleksandr Postylha Junior PHP Developer

Self-taught backend developer with more than two years of learning and continuous skills improvement processes. Proficient in basic programming concepts and tools: data structures, OOP paradigm, MVC and MTV patterns (for Laravel & Django respectively), debugger and version control usage, Unix-like operation systems and Bash scripting, relational databases (MySQL & SQLite), API design and integration, frontend elementary (web page structure and layout). Once started with interactive courses like Codecademy, I'm focused on practice and project-based learning process now. With patience and perseverance any issue may be solved (some of them just may take a bit longer than others $\ensuremath{\mbox{\ensuremath{\mbox{\sc b}}}\xspace$).

Eager to progress and make my own growing contribution to the result of experienced team hard work.

Portfolio:

- Test Task (REST API/PHP)
- Spotify Downloader (Laravel)
- Restaurant Inventory Management App (Django)
- Codewars katas (Python/PHP)

Work Experience:

 Lead Generation Executive & Strategist Nov 2021 - Feb 2022 Magnito.Agency

• Lead Generation Executive Apr 2021 - Nov 2021 ABM Cloud

• Lead Generation Specialist Apr 2020 - Apr 2021 Intellectsoft

• Researcher, Senior Researcher Арг 2018 - Арг 2020 CIENCE

Courses and Trainings:

- Codecademy (Intermediate Python 3, Django, CSS, HTML, etc.; more on LinkedIn)
- edX: Introduction to Linux by LinuxFoundation
- University of Waterloo: Computer Science Circles

Education:

- O.M.Beketov National University of Urban Economy Bachelor's degree, Management and Administration (2014 - 2018)
- National University of Kyiv-Mohyla Academy Applied Mathematics (2012 - 2014)